A Finding Aid to the Exhibition Records of the Contemporary Study Wing of the Finch College Museum of Art, 1943-1975, in the Archives of American Art AAA.finccoll
Archives of American Art
- Exhibition Files, 1943-1975; Series 4; 14.8 Linear feet Boxes 6-22, OV 24-25
  - "Forms in Metal" (1975) (Box 14)
    - Photographs of Artwork, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Press Releases and Clippings, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 34)
      Oversized clippings in box 22, folder 5.
    - Research, 1943-1974 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - "Four Contemporary African Artists" (not realized) (Box 14)
    - General File, 1962-1965 (Box 14, Folder 36-38)
    - Bank Presentation, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - "French Landscape Painters from Four Centuries" (1965-1966), Checklist, circa 1965 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - "Galaxy of Ladies: American Paintings from the Paul Magriel Collection" (1966) (Box 14)
    - Catalog, Press Release, Announcement, and Clippings, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - Paul Magriel Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - Photographs of Artwork (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - "Giacometti: The Complete Graphics" (1971) (Box 14)
    - Checklist, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - Correspondence and Contracts, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - Photographs and Catalog Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - Press Releases and Clippings, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - "Grafica Oggi: Contemporary Graphics from the Studio 2RC in Rome" (1974) (Box 14)
    - Catalog, Press Release and Clippings, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 49-50)
    - Insurance, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    - Notes and Photograph, circa 1974 (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - "Guerrero Stone Sculpture" (1965) (Box 14)
    - Catalog Checklist, circa 1965 (Box 14, Folder 53)
    - Catalog Drafts, circa 1965 (Box 14, Folder 54)
    - Correspondence, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 55)
    - Loan Correspondence, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 56)
    - Loan Forms, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 57-58)
    - Loan Valuation, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 59)
    - Photographs of Artwork, circa 1965 (Box 14, Folder 60)
    - Press Releases, Announcements, and Clippings (Box 14, Folder 61)
    - Receipts, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 62)
  - "Hans Richter Retrospective" (1968) (Box 15)
    - Announcement, Guest List, and Attendance Statistics, circa 1968 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Bills and Receipts, 1968-1969 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Catalog and Price List, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Clippings and Reviews, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, General, 1967-1968 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, Hans Richter, 1967-1971 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Film Program, 1947, 1967-1968 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Interview with Hans Richter, circa 1967; 1 sound tape reels (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Lists of Artworks, 1967-1968 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Loan Forms, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Photographs for Catalog, circa 1968 (Box 15, Folder 11-13)
    - Photographs of Installation, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Unidentified Sketch, undated (Box 15, Folder 15)
      Oversized sketch in box 22, folder 5.
    - Writings, circa 1968 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - "Homenatge a Joan Prat, by Joan Miro" (1972) (Box 15)
    - Correspondence, Insurance, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Printed Materials, 1971-1972 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - "Hugo Weber: A Retrospective Exhibition" (1975) (Binder 15)
    - Catalog, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Catalog Drafts, Notes, and Receipts, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, General, 1973-1975 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, Embassy of Switzerland, 1973-1975 (Box 15, Folder 22-23)
    - Lenders, circa 1975 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Photographs of Artwork, circa 1972-1975 (Box 15, Folder 25-26)
    - Photographs of Weber, circa 1973 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Press Release and Announcement, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Research, 1974-1975; Includes one sound cassette (Box 15, Folder 29)
      Contains a transcript and sound recoridng of an interview with Ruth Richards.
    - Swiss Society Party, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - "Images of an Era" (not realized), 1975 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - "Irish Directions" (not realized), 1974-1975 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - "Italian Visual Poetry" (1973) (Box 15)
    - Catalog, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence and Loan Documentation, 1972-1973 (Box 15, Folder 34-35)
    - Insurance Valuation, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Lists and Notes, circa 1973 (Box 15, Folder 37)
      Oversized list in OV 25.
    - Photographs of Installation, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Press Release, Announcement, and Clippings, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Printed Material, 1973 and undated (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - Proposal, circa 1972 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - "Jack Sonenberg" (not realized) (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - "Jacques Kaplan's Private Collection" (1969) (Box 15)
    - Catalog Drafts and Galleys, circa 1969 (Box 15, Folder 43)
      Oversized galleys housed in OV 25.
    - Letters and Receipts, 1968-1969 (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - Lists, circa 1969 (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - Loan Forms, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 46-47)
    - Photographs, circa 1969 (Box 15, Folder 48)
    - Press Release and Clippings, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 49)
      Oversized clipping in Box 22, folder 5.
  - "James Brooks Retrospective" (1975) (Box 15)
    - Bills and Receipts, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 50)
    - Catalog Drafts, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 51)
    - Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 15, Folder 52-53)
      See also research file for additional correspondence with Brooks.
    - Photographs of Artwork, circa 1975 (Box 15, Folder 54)
    - Press Release, Announcement, and Clippings, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 55)
    - Research, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 56-57)
    - Interview with Brooks and Janet Katz, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 58)
      Transcript only.
  - "Jan Cybis" (1966) (Box 16)
    - Catalog, Press Release, Announcement, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Clippings, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1964-1966 (Box 16, Folder 3-6)
    - Kazimir Gallery Artist Files (Box 16)
      - Jan Cybis, 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 7)
      - Henryk Stazewski, 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 8)
      - Jean Gorin, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Notes and Writings, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Photographs of Artwork, circa 1966 (Box 16, Folder 11-16)
    - Photographs for Catalog, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Photograph of Cybis and Warsaw Installation, 1959, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Receipts, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - "Josephine and Philip Bruno Collection" (1965-1966) (Box 16)
    - Catalog, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Clippings, 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence and Loan Forms, 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 22-23)
    - Lists, circa 1965 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Press Release and Announcement, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Photographs of Artwork, circa 1965 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Photographs of Installation Views, 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - "Lila Katzen: Rolled Steel Sculpture" (not realized), 1974-1975; 1970 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - "N-Dimensional Space" (1970) (Box 16)
    - Artist's Submission from Joel Stein, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 29)
      Oversized schematic drawings in OV 25.
    - Catalog, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Clippings, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 31)
      Oversized clippings in OV 25
    - Correspondence, 1969-1972 (Box 16, Folder 32-34)
    - Correspondence with Laser Lenders, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Discussion of Holography, 1970; 2 sound tape reels Includes transcript (Box 16, Folder 36)
      With Lloyd G. Cross, Allyn Z. Lite, and Gerald Thomas Bern Pethick
    - Interview with Margaret Benyon, circa 1970; 1 sound tape reels (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Loan Forms, Receipts, and Insurance, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Photographs, Negatives and Contact Sheets, circa 1970 (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Photographs, Prints and Transparencies, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 40)
      Oversized photographs in box 22, folder 6
    - Press Release and Publicity, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - Proposals and Budget, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - Research, circa 1965-1971 (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - Technical Specifications and Floor Plans, circa 1970 (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - Traveling Exhibition, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 45-46)
    - Unidentified Sketches, circa 1970 (Box 16, Folder 47)
      Possibly by G. Pethick
  - "New Materials, Impossible Art" (not realized), circa 1969 (Box 16, Folder 48-49)
  - "Patrick Ireland: 10 Years" (not realized), 1975 (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - Philip Pearlstein (1974) (Box 16)
    - Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 16, Folder 51)
    - Insurance, Shipping, and Receipts, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 52)
    - Insurance Claim, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - "Philip Pearlstein" (1974) (Box 17)
    - Lists, 1973-1974 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Loan Forms, 1973-1974 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Press Release, Publicity, and Clippings, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - "Posters by Artists" (1969) (Box 17)
    - Clippings, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Condition Reports, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1969-1973 (Box 17, Folder 6-7)
    - Lists, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 8-10)
    - Notes and Writings, circa 1969 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Photographs, circa 1969 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Posters, circa 1969 (Box 17, Folder 13)
      Oversized poster in box 22, folder 6
  - "Prints from Hollanders Workshop" (1972) (Box 17)
    - Correspondence, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Interview with Irwin Hollander, 1972 February 17 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Lists, circa 1972 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Loan Forms and Receipts, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Photographs, circa 1972 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Press Release and Clippings, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - "The Private Collection of Martha Jackson" (1973) (Box 17)
    - 15th Anniversary Celebration 1953-1968, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Condition Reports, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 17, Folder 22-23)
    - Interview with David Anderson, 1 Sound cassettes Includes transcript (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Lists, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Loan Forms and Receipts, 1973-1974 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Photographs of Installation, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Press Release, Announcement, and Clippings, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Theft of Arman Collage, 1973-1974 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - "Projected Art" (1966-1967) (Box 17)
    - Artist Biographies, circa 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Artist Files (Box 17)
      - Alexander Alexieff, 1966-1968 (Box 17, Folder 31)
      - Maurice Amar, 1966-1968 (Box 17, Folder 32)
      - Kenneth Anger, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 33)
      - Bruce Baille, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 34)
      - Paul Bartel, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 35)
      - Ilya Bolotowsky, 1966-1968 (Box 17, Folder 36)
      - Stan Brakhage, 1966-1968 (Box 17, Folder 37)
      - Robert Breer, 1966-1968 (Box 17, Folder 38)
      - David Brooks, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 39)
      - Peter Campus, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 40)
      - Bruce Connor, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 41)
      - James Davis, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 42)
      - Carmen D'Avino, 1966-1968 (Box 17, Folder 43)
      - Ed Emshwiller, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 44)
      - Jules Engel, 1964-1968 (Box 17, Folder 45)
        Oversized poster in box 22, folder 6.
      - Richard Geredasy and Tom McDonough, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 46)
      - Mordi Gerstein, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 47)
      - Leonard Glasser, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 48)
      - Red Grooms, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 49)
      - Hilary Harris, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 50)
      - Ian Hugo, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 51)
      - George Kuchar, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 52)
      - Dan McLaughlin, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 53)
      - Jonas Mekas, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 54)
      - Fred Mogubgub, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 55)
      - Robert Nelson, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 56)
      - Hans Richter, 1967-1969 (Box 17, Folder 57)
      - Stan Vanderbeek, 1966-1968 (Box 17, Folder 58)
        Includes a floor plan for a proposed, untitled, multi-channel installation work
      - Andy Warhol, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 59)
      - Jud Yalkut, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 60)
    - Bills, Receipts, and Price List, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 61)
    - Catalog Text, circa 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 62)
    - Clippings, 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 63)
    - Correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box 17, Folder 64-67)
    - Film Evaluations, circa 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 68)
    - Film Research, circa 1966-1968 (Box 17, Folder 69-72)
    - "Girl Behind the Lens", undated; 1 Film reels 16 mm (Box 17, Folder 73)
  - "Projected Art" (1966-1967) (Box 18)
    - Lists of Films and Filmmakers, circa 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 1-2)
    - New York State Council on the Arts, 1966-1968 (Box 18, Folder 3-4)
    - Photographs of Film Stills, circa 1967 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - "Projected Art: Artists at Work" (1971) (Box 18)
    - Artist Biographies, circa 1971 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Artist Biography Research, circa 1971 (Box 18, Folder 8-13)
      Oversized photocopied clippings housed in OV 25.
    - Clippings, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 18, Folder 15-20)
    - Film Procurement, 1969-1971 (Box 18, Folder 21-23)
    - Interview with Doris Chase, circa 1970; 1 sound tape reels (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Lists and Installation Instructions, circa 1971 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - New York State Council on the Arts Contracts, 1970-1971 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Notes and Research, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Photographs, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 28-29)
    - Press Releases and Announcement, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Video Recordings (Box 18)
      - Lynda Benglis, Kansas State Union Pieces, 1971; 1 Videoreels (½ inch) (Box 18, Folder 31, Item 1)
      - Michael Singer Building His Sculpture, "Balance III", 1971; 1 Videoreels (½ inch) (Box 18, Folder 31, Item 2)
      - Sam Wiener, circa 1971; 1 Videoreels (½ inch) (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - "René Bouché: Portraits of Figures in the Arts" (1967) (Box 18)
    - Bills and Receipts, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Catalog, Writings and Research, 1957-1967 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 35-36)
    - Homages to René Bouché, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 37)
      Oversized handwritten statement signed "Matta" in box 22, folder 6.
    - Lists, circa 1967 (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Loan Agreements, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 39-40)
    - Photographs of Artwork, circa 1967 (Box 18, Folder 41-42)
    - Photographs of Installation Views and Opening, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Press Release, Announcement, and Clippings, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 44)
      Oversized clippings in box 22, folder 6.
  - "Robert Monroe: Essence of Form" (1967) (Box 18)
    - Announcement and Clippings, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - Catalog Drafts and Notes, circa 1967 (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - Letter and Loan Form, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - Photographs of Artwork, circa 1967 (Box 18, Folder 48)
    - Photographs of Installation, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - "Salvation Army Art Collection" (1968), circa 1968 (Box 18, Folder 50)
  - "Schemata 7" (1967) (Box 18)
    - Announcement, Press Release, and Clippings, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 51)
      Oversized pamphlet in box 22, folder 6.
    - Artist Résumés, circa 1967 (Box 18, Folder 52)
    - Catalog and Catalog Drafts, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 53)
    - Correspondence and Notes, circa 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 54)
    - Interview Transcripts, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 55-56)
  - "Schemata 7" (1967) (Box 19)
    - Interviews (Box 19)
      - Will Insley, circa 1967; 1 sound tape reels (Box 19, Folder 1, Item 1)
      - Michael Kirby, circa 1967; 1 sound tape reels (Box 19, Folder 1, Item 2)
      - Les Levine, circa 1967; 1 sound tape reels (Box 19, Folder 2, Item 1)
      - Ursula Meyer, circa 1967; 1 sound tape reels (Box 19, Folder 2, Item 2)
      - Brian O'Doherty, circa 1967; 1 sound tape reels (Box 19, Folder 3, Item 1)
      - Charles Ross, circa 1967; 1 sound tape reels (Box 19, Folder 3, Item 2)
      - Tony Smith, circa 1967; 1 sound tape reels (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Loan Forms, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Photographs for Catalog, circa 1967 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Photographs of Artists and Artwork, circa 1967 (Box 19, Folder 7-8)
    - Schematic Drawings or Michael Kirby Installation, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - "Selections from the Permanent Collection" (1971) (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - "Selections from the Permanent Collection" (1974) (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - "Seven Swedish Painters" (1965) (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - "Sonia Sekula" (1972) (Box 19)
    - Catalog, Press Release, Announcement, and Clipping, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence and Receipts, 1971-1972 (Box 19, Folder 14-16)
    - Customs, 1971-1972 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Lists, 1971-1972 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - "The Story of Christmas" (1968) (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - "Talk Out!" (1973) (Box 19)
    - Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Interview with Douglas Davis, 1972 December; 1 Sound cassettes Includes transcript (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Interview with Jane Davis, circa 1972; 1 Sound cassettes Includes transcript (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Interview with Russ Connor, circa 1972; 1 Sound cassettes Includes transcript (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Photographs from Broadcast, circa 1972 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Press Releases and Douglas Davis Catalog and CV, 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - "Studies in Black and White Videotape #3", 1972; 1 Videoreels (½ inch) (Box 19, Folder 26, Item 1)
    - "Studies in Color Videotape II", 1972; 1 Videoreels (½ inch) (Box 19, Folder 26, Item 2)
  - "The Troubles: An Artist's Document of Ulster" (1972-1973) (Box 19)
    - General File, 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Interview with Les Levine, 1972; 1 Sound cassettes (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Press Release and Clippings, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - "Towers" (1970) (Box 19)
    - Clippings, 1969-1970 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Guide to Exhibition and its Installation, circa 1970; 1 sound tape reels (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Photographs, circa 1970 (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Press Releases, Flyers, and Lists, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - "Twentieth Century Italian Art from the Carlo F. Bilotti Collection" (1967) (Box 19)
    - Catalog Drafts, circa 1967 (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Clippings, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - Lists, circa 1967 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - "Twentieth Century Italian Art from the Carlo F. Bilotti Collection" (1967) (Box 20)
    - Photographs of Artwork, circa 1967 (Box 20, Folder 1-2)
    - Photographs of Installation, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Press Release, Catalog, and Announcement, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - "Twice as Natural: 19th Century American Genre Painting" (1973-1974) (Box 20)
    - Bills, 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Catalog, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Clippings, 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 8-11)
    - Insurance, 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Loan Dispersal, 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Loan Forms and Receipts, 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 14-16)
  - "Twice as Natural: 19th Century American Genre Painting" (1973-1974) (Box 21)
    - Notes, circa 1973 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - "Two Aspects of an Illusion" (1971-1972) (Box 21)
    - Catalog Drafts, circa 1971 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Catalog Copyright Registration, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Clippings, Press Release, and Announcement, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 4)
      Oversized clipping and poster in OV 25
    - Correspondence and Résumés, 1971-1972 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Insurance, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Interview with Michael Mazur, circa 1971; 1 sound tape reels Includes transcript; 1 Sound cassettes Includes transcript (Box 21, Folder 7)
      Sound tape reel contains part 1 of interview, and sound cassette contains part 2.
    - Interview with Paul Gedeohn, circa 1971; 1 Sound cassettes Includes transcript (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Photographs, circa 1971 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - "Women in the Arts Festival" (1972) (Box 21)
    - Artist Information, circa 1972 (Box 21, Folder 10)
      Oversized poster in OV 25
    - Clippings, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Lists, circa 1972 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Loan Forms, Receipts, and Insurance, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Press Releases, Announcements, and Flyers, circa 1972 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Oversized Photographs from "American Art Deco Architecture" Exhibition, from box 6, folder 27, circa 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Oversized Materials from "Art Deco" Exhibition, from box 6 folders 30 and 35, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Oversized Clipping from "Art from Finland" Exhibition, from box 8 folder 3, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Oversized Materials from "Destruction Art" Exhibition, from box 13, folders 2, 14, and 16, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Oversized Materials from "Documentation" Exhibition, from box 13, folders 20 and 31, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Oversized Materials from "The Dominant Woman" Exhibition, from box 13, folders 33, 35, 37, and 51, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Oversized Clippings from "Energy Sculpture" Exhibition, from box 14, folder 4, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Oversized Materials from "Forms in Metal" Exhibition, from box 14, folders 34 and 35, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Oversized Sketch from "Hans Richter Retrospective," from box 15, folder 15, undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Oversized Clipping from "Jacques Kaplan's Private Collection" exhibition, from box 15, folder 49, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Oversized Photographs from "N-Dimensional Space" Exhibition, from box 16, folder 40, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Oversized Poster from "Posters by Artists" Exhibition, from box 17, folder 13, circa 1969 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Oversized Poster from "Projected Art" Exhibition, from box 17, folder 45, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Oversized Materials from "Rene Bouche: Portraits of Figures in the Arts" Exhibition, from box 18, folders 37 and 44, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Oversized Pamphlet from "Schemata 7" Exhibition, from box 18, folder 51, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Oversized Posters from "Art in Process: The Visual Development of a Collage," from box 9, folder 44, 1964-1965 (Box OV 23)
  - Oversized Clippings from "Art in Jewelry" Exhibition, from box 8, folders 20 and 42, 1965-1966 (Box OV 23)
  - Oversized Clippings from "Art Deco" Exhibition, from box 7, folders 31 and 45, 1970-1972 (Box OV 23)
  - Oversized Posters from "The Dominant Woman" Exhibition, from box 13, folder 53, circa 1968 (Box OV 23)
  - Oversized Posters from "Art in Process: The Visual Development of a Collage," from box 9 folders 43, 54, and 64, 1968 (Box OV 24)
  - Oversized Galleys for "Art in Process IV" Exhibition Catalog, from box 10, folder 9, 1969 (Box OV 24)
  - Oversized Clippings from "Art in Series" Exhibition, from box 10, folder 28, 1967 (Box OV 24)
  - Oversized Photographs for "Art Nouveau" Exhibition Catalog, from box 10, folder 59, circa 1969 (Box OV 24)
  - Oversized Materials from "Artists Select" Exhibition, from box 10, folder 61 and box 11, folders 7 and 49, 1966 (Box OV 24)
  - Oversized Notes from Douglas Davis installation, from box 11, folder 57, circa 1971 (Box OV 24)
  - Oversized Magazine from "Artists Videotape Performances" Exhibition, from box 11, folder 62, 1971 (Box OV 24)
  - Oversized Clippings from "Destruction Art" Exhibition, from box 13, folders 3 and 4, 1966, 1968 (Box OV 24)
  - Oversized Draft of the "Les Formes Vivantes: Alexander Archipenko" Exhibition Catalog, from box 14, folder 21, 1965 (Box OV 25)
  - Oversized List from "Italian Visual Poetry" exhibition, from box 15, folder 37, circa 1973 (Box OV 25)